Guide to the Malcolm Goldstein Papers MSS.350
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE Series III
  - Subseries C: Ephemera
    - 1982-1983: [Jackson Mac Low retrospective; D.C. Space; Ear Magazine benefit concert] (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - 1983: UIT Krant [Dutch], November, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - 1983-1984: [Festival D'Automne], Summer 1983- Summer 1984 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - 1983: [Andere Avant Garde], Fall, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - 1983-1984: [Holland Tour], Summer 1983- Summer 1984 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - 1983-1985: [Ornette Coleman Festival; P.S.1] (Folder 2)
    - 1984-1985: [Holland Tour], Fall 1984- Summer 1985 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - 1985: [Mobius 'Five Concerts of Improvised Music'] (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - 1985: ["...that hung like fire on heaven"; "On New Music"] (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - 1986: [Strange Mutations at the Kitchen], January, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - 1986: ["Breath River Route"; NuArts] (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - 1987: [Visual Scores], September 8-October 18, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - 1987-1988: [Absolute Cow; New Music America] (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - 1988: ["Cycladic Imprints" with Carolee Schneeman] (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - 1990: [Europe Tour], Summer, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - 2001: [Festival International de Nouvelle Danse], June 10, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - 2004: [Subtropics], March-April, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - 2006: [Barre Phillips; "Hello Goodbye Mr. Bailey"] (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - 2009: ["Topography of a Sound Mind"] (Box 48, Folder 16)